Ratchapol Marmongkol

Github: github.com/mratchapol Email: ratchapolhappy@gmail.com

Mobile: +66 888712331 Address: Lak Si, Bangkok



SUMMARY

Equipped with German Language Major, Computer Science Minor, plus experience in Master's in Computer Science, I have passion for Java and I am seeking Java developer role. I have 3-year experience in writing Java, still 0 years in career. I am highly adaptable and do not stop improving myself. Proud to add that I am also language enthusiast.

EDUCATION

2022 - 2024 **Master of Computer Science**

Bachelor in Liberal Arts, German Language 2018 - 2021

Thammasat University; GPA: 3.34

Thammasat University; GPA: 3.33

Triam Udom Suksa School 2015 - 2017 English-German program

SKILLS

🖏 , SQL, HTML (confident) | CSS, Python, C++, JavaScript Languages

- Strong understanding of principles of OOP

- Good understanding of Collections framework and basic data structure

- Good understanding of SQL

- Good understanding of Maven, Spring Boot annotations that handle REST API, dependency injection, and basic exceptions

Spring Boot Opening Pandas, Numpy, Scikit-Learn Frameworks

 Tools MySQL, PostgreSQL, Git **Platforms** Eclipse, NetBeans, AWS

- ETL data pipeline using AWS EC2, S3, Cloud9, Glue, Athena, and QuickSight

 Other skills Reading Java Doc skill, Unix Command, Adaptability

English TOEIC 795, German Goethe-Zertifikat B1, Japanese JLPT N5

WORK EXPERIENCE

Work and Travel Program in the US

May 2024 - September 2024

Performed houseman and housekeeping tasks in hotel

Project Coordinator, Pasona Recruitment (Thailand)

Jan 2022 - Sept 2023

- Liaised with HR managers and officers from over 20 companies, scheduled and followed up on meetings
- Served as point of communication between internal and external stakeholders
- Manage project-related paperwork, quotations, invoices, receipts from more than 10 vendors, including monitoring expenses and timeline

Internship, Directorate of Intelligence, Royal Thai Air Force. June2021 - July 2021

· Translated and summaried news and magazine related to military and air force

CERTIFICATES

